<?xml version="1.0"?>
<product comment="A CafePress product is a type of merchandise customized with a user's designs. Completed products are sellable." id="0" name="Baseball Jersey" merchandiseId="38" sellPrice="16.99" marketplacePrice="22.00" currencyName="US Dollar" currencyCode="USD" currencySymbol="$" description="Our 100% cotton Baseball Jersey is a sporty hit with both men and women whether you're in the game or just looking the part in great run-around casual-wear.  Choose red, blue or black sleeves. &#xD;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;6.1 oz. 100% heavyweight cotton&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Standard fit&lt;/li&gt;&#xD;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;3/4 length contrasting raglan sleeves&lt;/li &gt;&lt;/ul&gt;" memberId="0" storeId="" sectionId="0" defaultOrientation="Normal" defaultPerspective="Front" basePrice="16.99" shortCaption="Baseball Jersey" defaultCaption="Baseball Jersey" shortDescription="Jersey" categoryId="111" categoryCaption="Shirts (long)" stockAvailability="In Stock." stockAvailabilityStatusId="1" merchandiseAvailability="Limited Edition Item" merchandiseAvailabilityStatusId="2" defaultProductUri="http://images0.cafepress.com/product/0v0_240x240_Front_Color-BlackWhite.jpg" additionalPhotoCount="4" isCalendar="false" isBook="false" isCD="false" isAudioCD="false" isPoster="false" legacyHeightValue="0" legacyWidthValue="0" sortPriority="0" isSellable="true">
  <comment key="colors" fieldType="optional" defaultValue="">Represents one of the available colors of a type of merchandise. Product definitions may limit what colors are available for sale and specify a default.</comment>
  <comment key="sizes" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">Represents one of the available sizes of a type of merchandise.</comment>
  <comment key="id" fieldType="optional" defaultValue="0">The unique numeric identifier of the product. And id of 0 indicates a new product. Upon successfully saving a new product, the product definition will be returned with an assigned id.</comment>
  <comment key="name" fieldType="required" defaultValue="">The name of the product.</comment>
  <comment key="merchandiseId" fieldType="required" defaultValue="0">The id of the merchandise of this product. Products are merchandise configured with designs. The merchandise id cannot be changed for a particular product after the product is saved.</comment>
  <comment key="sellPrice" fieldType="optional" defaultValue="basePrice">The price of the product in the product owner's store. sellPrice must be equal to or greater than the base price.</comment>
  <comment key="marketplacePrice" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The marketplace price of the product based on its underlying merchandise merchandise.</comment>
  <comment key="currencyName" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The currency of the prices shown. Currency is determined by the location of the host location of the downloading or by using the location parameter to specify a location.</comment>
  <comment key="currencyCode" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The currency code of the prices shown. Currency is determined by the location of the host location of the downloading or by using the location parameter to specify a location.</comment>
  <comment key="currencySymbol" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The currency symbol of the prices shown. Currency is determined by the location of the host location of the downloading or by using the location parameter to specify a location.</comment>
  <comment key="description" fieldType="optional" defaultValue="">The editable description of the product.</comment>
  <comment key="memberId" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The read-only memberId of the product. A product may only belong to one CafePress member (i.e. user/shopkeeper.) The member id of a product can only change if the product is transfered from an anonymous member to a real member. See &lt;b&gt;authentication.transferAnonymousUser.cp&lt;/b&gt;</comment>
  <comment key="storeId" fieldType="optional" defaultValue="">The alpha-numeric storeId of the product. A product may be assigned to any store of the owning member, provided store quoata levels are not reached. The storeId should be left 0 omitted for anonymous users. If omitted a storeId will default to the first Create &amp; Buy store (a store with isSelfBuy="true"), or one will be created if it does not exist.</comment>
  <comment key="storeName" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The name of the store referenced by storeId. This is here for convenience. Use store.findStore.cp for full store data.</comment>
  <comment key="sectionId" fieldType="optional" defaultValue="0">The numeric store sectionId of the product. A product may be assigned to any section of the given storeId, provided store quoata levels are not reached. A sectionId of 0 indicates that the product should go in the top-level section of the store, which always has a sectionId of 0.</comment>
  <comment key="sectionName" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The name of the section referenced by sectionId. This is here for convenience. Use store.findStoreSection.cp for full section data.</comment>
  <comment key="defaultOrientation" fieldType="optional" defaultValue="merchandise.defaultOrientation">The string identifier of the default orientation of a product. This attribute only matters for products of merchandise that have multiple options for how a design is applied to a media region (e.g. horizontal or vertical.) Product with multiple orientations will list orientation options in the merchandise and product definitions.</comment>
  <comment key="defaultSize" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The numeric size identifier of the default size of a product.</comment>
  <comment key="defaultPerspective" fieldType="optional" defaultValue="merchandise.defaultPerspective">The default perspective of the underlying merchandise. This denotes what perspective is shown by the defaultProductUri. Only merchandise with front and back perspectives can be set. Other merchandise, such as calendars, are read-only.</comment>
  <comment key="basePrice" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The base price of the underlying merchandise. The base price is the minimum sellPrice you can set for a product. Be aware that some product options, notably extra large sizes, can increase the final sell price of the product.</comment>
  <comment key="shortCaption" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The short descripton of the underlying merchandise.</comment>
  <comment key="defaultCaption" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The description of the underlying merchandise.</comment>
  <comment key="shortDescription" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The short description of the underlying merchandise, limited to 50 characters.</comment>
  <comment key="categoryId" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The category id of the underlying merchandise.</comment>
  <comment key="categoryCaption" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The category caption of the underlying merchandise.</comment>
  <comment key="stockAvailability" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The current availability of the underlying merchandise. See stockAvailabilityId for the values.</comment>
  <comment key="stockAvailabilityStatusId" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The numeric id indicating the current availability of the underlying merchandise. The values are as follows: 1	In Stock., 2	In Stock, will ship in 2-3 business days (shipped separately), 5	Immediate electronic delivery, 100	No Longer Available, 101	Temporarily Out of Stock, will ship in 2-3 weeks, 102	Not Available for Individual Purchase, 103	Temporarily Out of Stock, 107	Pre-Order, this item will ship in 2-3 weeks. Your order will not be shipped until this item is available., 110	For Design Only, Not For Sale, 111	Will ship in 5-6 business days.  All Custom Postage orders are subject to image review by Stamps.com.Please Note - We cannot guarantee delivery time for Stamps., 112	Dark Apparel will ship in a minimum of 5 business days., 113	In stock.  Usually ships within 3-5 business days., 114	In Stock, will ship in 5 business days, 115	No Longer Available/Non Reportable, 116	In Stock, will ship in 2 business days, 117	In stock, will ship in 2-3 business days. Note: Matte paper is on back-order and will ship in 1 week., 118	Available immediately</comment>
  <comment key="merchandiseAvailability" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The string based on the underlying merchandise indicating limitations on creating products of the merchandise. See merchandiseAvailabilityStatusId for the values.</comment>
  <comment key="merchandiseAvailabilityStatusId" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The read-only numeric id based on the underlying merchandise indicating limitations on creating products of the merchandise. The values are as follows (Premium indicates premium shops only): 0	Not available to add, 1	Premium Item, 2	Limited Edition Item, 3	All Stores | Permanent Item</comment>
  <comment key="defaultProductUri" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The default URI to render an image of the product. This URI is based on the default perspective and default color (if applicable.) Designs assigned to the media configurations in the default perspective will appear.</comment>
  <comment key="wildcardProductUri" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The URI to render an image of the product.  This URI places CSS-style wildcards in place of the perspective and color (if applicable) to allow you to replace the wildcard with one of the available values of your choice.  The wildcard tells you where to find the possible values in the product XML (e.g. (color id) means look at the color elements and chose one of the id attributes.)</comment>
  <comment key="marketplaceUri" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">A URL showing the product on its marketplace page.</comment>
  <comment key="storeUri" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">A URL showing the product on its store page.</comment>
  <comment key="additionalPhotoCount" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The property representing the number of available photos of the underlying merchandise.</comment>
  <comment key="isCalendar" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The property that returns true if the underlying merchandise is any type of calendar.</comment>
  <comment key="isBook" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">This is true if the underlying merchandise is a book. Books are not fully supported by the API. Though typical properties can be listed, no book-specific data is available.</comment>
  <comment key="isCD" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">This is true if the underlying merchandise is a CD. CDs are not fully supported by the API. Though typical properties can be listed, no CD-specific data is available.</comment>
  <comment key="isAudioCD" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">This is true if the underlying merchandise is an Audio CD. CDs are not fully supported by the API. Though typical properties can be listed, no CD-specific data is available.</comment>
  <comment key="isPoster" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">This is true if the underlying merchandise is any type of poster.</comment>
  <comment key="legacyHeightValue" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">A legacy property. For internal use only.</comment>
  <comment key="legacyWidthValue" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">A legacy property. For internal use only.</comment>
  <comment key="sortPriority" fieldType="optional" defaultValue="0">The sort value of a product within its store and section between 0 and 100 inclusive, where 100 is highest. If the value is set to the same value as another product in the store or section, the two products relative ordering will be nondeterministic.</comment>
  <comment key="isSellable" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">Indicates whether a product is complete and is thus sellable. Products are complete when they contain all required media configurations have designs.</comment>
  <color comment="Represents one of the available colors of a type of merchandise. Product definitions may limit what colors are available for sale and specify a default." id="4" name="Black/White" default="true" colorSwatchUrl="/content/marketplace/img/swatches/swatch_baseballjersey_blackwhite.gif">
    <comment key="id" fieldType="required" defaultValue="">The unique id of the color, unique accross all merchandise.</comment>
    <comment key="name" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The name of the color, unique within the merchandise.</comment>
    <comment key="default" fieldType="optional" defaultValue="false">Indicates if the color is the default color for the merchandise</comment>
    <comment key="colorSwatchUrl" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">A URL showing a swatch of the color.</comment>
  </color>
  <color id="5" name="Red/White" default="false" colorSwatchUrl="/content/marketplace/img/swatches/swatch_baseballjersey_redwhite.gif" />
  <color id="8" name="Blue/White" default="false" colorSwatchUrl="/content/marketplace/img/swatches/swatch_baseballjersey_bluewhite.gif" />
  <size comment="Represents one of the available sizes for the merchandise." id="4" name="Small" fullName="Small" shortName="S" default="true" priceDifference="0" displaySellPrice="$16.99" displayDiscountPrice="$16.99" />
  <size id="5" name="Medium" fullName="Medium" shortName="M" default="false" priceDifference="0" displaySellPrice="$16.99" displayDiscountPrice="$16.99" />
  <size id="6" name="Large" fullName="Large" shortName="L" default="false" priceDifference="0" displaySellPrice="$16.99" displayDiscountPrice="$16.99" />
  <size id="7" name="X-Large" fullName="X-Large" shortName="XL" default="false" priceDifference="0" displaySellPrice="$16.99" displayDiscountPrice="$16.99" />
  <size id="8" name="2X-Large" fullName="2X-Large (+$3.00)" shortName="2XL" default="false" priceDifference="3" displaySellPrice="$19.99" displayDiscountPrice="$19.99" />
  <perspective comment="Perspectives describe available views of a product, which correspond directly to the perspectives of the underlying merchandise. Perspective definitions offer URLs use to visualize the product for the given perspective. Wildcard URLs are also offered which allow you insert the color and/or or orientation for the product when applicable. The wildcards follow CSS formatting to indicate where in the product XML definition you can find the applicable values" name="Front" pixelWidth="480" pixelHeight="480" sortOrder="0" isEditable="true" defaultMediaRegion="FrontCenter" label="F" wildcardProductUri="http://images0.cafepress.com/nocache/product/0v0_240x240_Front_Color-BlackWhite.jpg">
    <comment key="wildcardProductUri" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">A URL showing the product with this perspective. The URL may have a wildcard placeholder for the color indicated by (color id) if the merchandise supports multiple colors.</comment>
    <comment key="name" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The name of the perspective, unique within the merchandise.</comment>
    <comment key="pixelWidth" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The width in pixels of the perspective rendering.</comment>
    <comment key="pixelHeight" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The height in pixels of the perspective rendering.</comment>
    <comment key="sortOrder" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The sort order of the perspective relative to others.</comment>
    <comment key="isEditable" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">Indicates whether the mediaConfigurations of products corresponding to the mediaRegions in this perspective can receive a design. Most mediaConfigurations can hold designs but a few are limited to special sales channels.</comment>
    <comment key="defaultMediaRegion" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">Indicates the default mediaRegion for this perspective, meaning the corresponding mediaConfiguration is the default mediaConfiguration used by the web site designer.</comment>
    <comment key="label" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">A label used in creating the URL of the for the perspective.</comment>
    <showsMediaRegion>FrontCenter</showsMediaRegion>
    <showsMediaRegion>FrontPocket</showsMediaRegion>
  </perspective>
  <perspective name="Back" pixelWidth="480" pixelHeight="480" sortOrder="0" isEditable="true" defaultMediaRegion="BackCenter" label="B" wildcardProductUri="http://images0.cafepress.com/nocache/product/0v0_240x240_Back_Color-BlackWhite.jpg">
    <showsMediaRegion>BackShoulder</showsMediaRegion>
    <showsMediaRegion>BackCenter</showsMediaRegion>
  </perspective>
  <mediaConfiguration comment="MediaConfiguration represents a placement of a design on a product. All products have one or more mediaConfigurations. MediaConfigurations correspond one-to-one to the mediaRegions of the product's merchandise. If more mediaConfigurations are given a design id than is supported by the underlying merchandise, then only the certain designs will appear on the product. When saving a product, it is only necessary to specify mediaConfigurations to which you are applying a design id. You can save a product without assigning designs to media configurations. Certain products, like calendars, are not sellable until all of the mediaConfigurations have a design." dpi="100" height="10" width="10" name="BackCenter" designId="0" alignment="TopCenter" isEditable="true" perspectives="Back">
    <comment key="dpi" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The DPI of the media configuration based on the size of the design assigned to the media configuration.</comment>
    <comment key="height" fieldType="optional" defaultValue="0, forces the largest possible size for the design.">The assignable height in inches that the design should occupy of the mediaConfiguration. In most cases you can leave this value unassigned to maximize the design with the mediaConfiguration. However, if you want the design to take up a smaller part of the mediaConfiguration area, you can set the value lower than that of the corresponding merchandise.mediaRegion.height. Note that if the design's aspect ratio does not match that of the mediaConfiguration's, based on corresponding merchandise.mediaRegion, then the mediaConfiguration height and width will shrink to match the design's aspect ratio. For example if the dimensions of a poster's mediaRegion is 10 inches wide by 8 inches high, and your design is 1000 pixels by 1000 pixels and the mediaConfiguration is 100 DPI (i.e. the design is 10 inches by 10 inches), then mediaConfiguration's size will be reduced to 8 inches by 8 inches to accomodate the full square design. If the design does not occupy the entire media region, such as in this case, then the alignment of the design will depend on the corresponding merchandise.mediaRegion.defaultAlignment property. You may reduce the mediaConfiguration height to the minimum designated by the corresponding merchandise.mediaRegion.minimumHeight. If you set the height too large it will be maximized to the greatest possible height, and likewise too small a height will be minimized.</comment>
    <comment key="width" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The width in inches of the design with the mediaConfiguration in ratio to the height property. Only the height can be set. The width is calculated given the height and the media configuration's DPI and other constraints. See height.</comment>
    <comment key="name" fieldType="required" defaultValue="">The name of the mediaConfiguration, corresponding to one of the underlying merchandise's mediaRegions.</comment>
    <comment key="designId" fieldType="optional" defaultValue="">The id of the design assigned to the mediaConfiguration. The design id can be updated to any id belong to the owner of the product.</comment>
    <comment key="alignment" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The alignment of the design within the merchandise's mediaRegion. Most merchandise only has one possible value. Cylindrical merchandise like mugs have 9 possible values. See the product's corresponding merchandise definition for the defaultAlignmnetThe possible values are TopLeft, TopCenter, TopRight, MiddleLeft, MiddleCenter, MiddleRight, BottomLeft, BottomCenter, BottomRight.</comment>
    <comment key="isEditable" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">Indicates whether this mediaConfiguration can receive a design. Most mediaConfigurations can hold designs but a few are limited to special sales channels.</comment>
    <comment key="perspectives" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">Lists perspectives that show this mediaConfiguration</comment>
  </mediaConfiguration>
  <mediaConfiguration dpi="100" height="10" width="10" name="FrontCenter" designId="0" alignment="TopCenter" isEditable="true" perspectives="Front" />
  <productImage comment="Represents a particular rendering of a product, by perspective, color, and image size. Color is optional. All attributes are read-only" colorId="4" perspectiveName="Front" imageSize="480" productUrl="http://images0.cafepress.com/product/0v0_480x480_Front_Color-BlackWhite.jpg">
    <comment key="colorId" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The unique id of the color of those available for the underlying merchandise.</comment>
    <comment key="perspectiveName" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The unique name of a perspective of the underlying merchandise.</comment>
    <comment key="imageSize" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The size in pixels of the width and height of the image.</comment>
    <comment key="productUrl" fieldType="readonly" defaultValue="">The URL of the product image.</comment>
  </productImage>
  <productImage colorId="5" perspectiveName="Front" imageSize="480" productUrl="http://images0.cafepress.com/product/0v0_480x480_Front_Color-RedWhite.jpg" />
</product>